Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contact Sheet 14633, 1968 November 16
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Navy.
- Contact Sheet 14634, 1968 November 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy - Capt. Edward J. Snyder Jr. - printed November 16, '68 Pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #6 - 10 shots of 16 inch shells being lowered below deck and loaded aboard ship. 2 shots Capt. Snyder. 3 shots chief master at arms Lyle Chastain (for story on battleship sailors). 3 shots Bt2 Stewart Hall tends being below the ships waterline. 2 shots Fn John Twomey works on board.
- Contact Sheet 14635, 1968 November 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy - story printed November / 16 / '68 / Pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet No. 9 - Entire sheet is composed of sailors, hoisting 16 inch ammo aboard and lowering it below decks.
- Contact Sheet 14636, 1968 November 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy - printed November / 16 / 1968.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: sheet #10 in sequence - 1 shot sailor peering at N. Vietnam with special binoculars. 2 shot of 16 inch turret of New Jersey at angle. 2 shots of 5 inch gun turret on New Jersey. 1 shot of 16 inch turrets on N.J. 6 shots of 5 inch gun turrets on N.J. 1 shot of sailor sitting inside 16 inch gun turret - 16 inch shells note swastika and symbols for war resisters league on nose of shell - Gm3 Dave Croft watches sailor set fuses 16 inch shells - loading powder into 16 inch guns - 16 inch shell being readied for loading - gun Captain Gmg3 Greg Wickoff pauses for a breather beside 16" shells - 16 inch shell, backgound is breech of 16 inch gun - New Jersey with 16 inch guns at angle.
- Contact Sheet 14637, 1968 November 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy - story printed November / 16 / 1968 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #11 in sequence - 1 shot Gmg1 Delos Luchs watches proceedings from inside 16 inch turret. 2 shots 16 inch shell ready for loading. 1 shot sailor setting fuze on shell. 1 shot 16 inch shell actually being rammed inside breech of gun as Gmg3 Greg Wickoff turns his head. 2 shots of powder being loaded into 16 inch gun. 2 shots of 16 inch shell being loaded into gun. 2 shots of 16 inch shells lying below decks, awaiting their turn to be fired. 1 shot 16 inch shell (foreground) and breech of 16 inch gun (background). 3 shots underexposed. 1 shot Chief Harold L. Sykes as he climbs inside hatch of 16 inch gun. 1 shot of powder being rammed inside gun as Gm3 Wickoff (Left and Gm3 Dave Croft stand by right stand by).
- Contact Sheet 14647, 1968 October 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - Cpl. John Belknap.
- Contact Sheet 14648, 1968 November 9
  ENVELOPE TEXT: American Vietnam relations - women - printed November/ 9 / '68.
- Contact Sheet 14649, 1968 November 2
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam night life - Saigon bar story - contact sheet A - printed Nov. / 2 / '68.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Night life sheet A - printed November 2, 1968 - P5 Pac.
- Contact Sheet 14650, 1968 November 2
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - military police - traffic cops - Sp4 Tom Leighty - Sp4 Gary Reynolds - traffic accidents - printed Nov./ 2 / '68 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Pictures for traffic cop story - Two frames Sp4 Tom Leighty pointing to scene of five fatality accidents on map. Two frames Leighty examining damage to taxi after accident. Two frames (left to right) Leighty and Sp4 Gary Reynolds with their AI kit. Overall scenes of traffic accident with Leighty taking down information from driver involved in wreck, checking out truck, trying to quiet angry taxi driver. Various shots of Saigon traffic.
- Contact Sheet 14651, 1968 November 2
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SSGT Vincent Angus - Army US NCOs - story printed 2nd Nov. '68- see story p. 3 - no pic. Used.
- Contact Sheet 14652, 1968 October 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Charles Crow - Narcotics - October / 19 / '68 / pac - story without picture printed.
- Contact Sheet 14733, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: civilians - Vietman - traffic - not printed.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Canh Sat Ballet - Dance of the Vietnamese Cop - Reynolds - Canh Sat directing traffic on the intersection of Tu Do and Le Thanh Ton streets in downtown Saigon. He was whipping his arms around and dancing like he was doing a ballet or maybe a slow-motion Spanish dance. Kind of unusual for a Vietnamese Cop. Most of them just stand there and wave or else (those that've been under American MP influence) wave the traffic on in an approved Provost-Marshal General's School fashion. This guy has his own style -- actually seems to enjoy directing traffic.
- Contact Sheet 14734, 1968 November 30
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Capt. Gary Herman - Pvt. Edgar J. Mines Jr. - C. A. Branum (theft) - MP guard Sp4 John A. Voltraggio - Capt William C. Lanham - Prisoners US army - riots - printed November/ 30 / '68 / Pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Nov. 9 - Photos for Mines Trial - Frame 6: Defence Lawyer Capt. Gary Herman (left) and Pvt Edgar J. Mines Jr. 7: Same as 6. 8: Civilian prisoner C. A. Branum (left), MP Guard Sp4 John A. Voltraggio (center), Prosecutor Capt. William C. Lanham. 11: A cocky Mines clowns for the camera by showing off handcuffs. He was leaving courtroom building at the end of the first day of trial. It was a two-day trial.
- Contact Sheet 14735, 1968 December 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Sgt. Maj. William Woolridge - Vietnam NCOs - printed December / 7 / '68 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Oct. 19 - ID contact sheet F - All pictures of man marked with red box are of Sgt Maj Wooldridge, for interview feature with him. Three pictures marked with X are of a sign at Tan Son Nhut AB, with arrows pointing to Paris, etc. If it will blow up, it might make a wild picture.
- Contact Sheet 14763, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam mail - Sgt. Curtis Young - Vietnam officers - Lt. Col. Theodore Schulz - sheet A - mail inspectors.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for story about mail inspectors - Sheet A in sequence: 13 shots Sgt Curtis Young inspecting packages with mine detector. 3 shots of GIs mailing packages at APO. 4 shots Lt Col Theodore Schulz beside mailbox. 4 shots of postal clerks at work.
- Contact Sheet 14764, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Australians - gunner taking a shower.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheets for stories on the Aussies - Roll#5 in sequence: 2 shots of 105 firing. Next 12 frames are for Man on the Street. 2 shots 2/1t Bernie Bryon. 2 shots gunner Grahme Collins. 2 shots gunner Bob Cane. 2 shots gunner Len Ketelaar. 2 shtos gunner Dave Thomas. 2 shots gunner Kim Robertson. 2 shots 2/1t Bernie Bryon grabbling a quick siesta. 2 shots readying 105 shells for fire mission. 2 shots tightening fuzes on 105 shells. 3 more shots of readying 105 shells for firing mission. 3 shots of digger.
- Contact Sheet 14765, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - NCOs Sgt. William Biglands - foreign troops (Australian) - Aussie pix - sheet #1 - Graham Collins - Kim Robertson - Phil Smith.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheet for stories on the Aussies - 4 shots gunners Grahame Collins (left) and Kim Robertson (right) firing 105 Howitzer. 1 shot gunner Phil Smith holding 105 shell. 3 more shots Collins & Robertson firing 105s -- note 1st shot in series Robertson has just pulled still hot shell casing out of breech of 105 and is in left hand. 1 shot of part of Flinders. Note 105 firing in center background. 3 shots of Chinook helicopter landing with slingload. 1 shot gunner Laurie Owen sighting through compass. 3 shots gunners at work cleaning 105. 5 shots of volleyball game between firing missions. 1 shot of 105 pointing up at high angle. 5 shots of injured volleyball player being carried off of the field. 1 shot of gun and sleeping areas. Diggers sleep in holes under the tarps. 1 shot gunner uncartoning 105 shell. 2 shots of 105s firing. 1 shot of Sgt William Biglands note tattoo on top of arm at shoulder which says: Only the drunks survive, Malaya 1958. 1 more shot of 105 firing.
- Contact Sheet 14766, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: 2nd Lt. Bernie Bryon - Pete Jenkins - Aussie pix - sheet #2 - Vietnam officers - foreign troops (Australian).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #2 in sequence: 1 shot of diggers being served hot chow, which sometimes occurs once a day. 1 shot 2/lt Bernie Bryon talking to the guns by intercom from the CP. 2 shots digger shaving. Gunner Pete Jenkins's reflection in the mirror as he shaves - lance bombadier Kevin Scrimshaw tightening recoil mechanism on 105.
- Contact Sheet 14767, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - foreign troops - Aussie pix - sheet #3.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #3 in sequence: 16 shots of night fire mission. 17 shots of New Zealand Infantryman moving through the scrub (jungle) near Flinders.
- Contact Sheet 14768, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Gen. Andrew J. Goodpaster - Capt. Jesse C. Johnson - awards + decorations.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Nov. 18 - ID for contact sheet no.4 -- 9th Div. award ceremony - Frames 8 through 13 and Frames 15: Ceremony at which Capt. Jesse L. Johnson received Silver Star from Gen. Andrew J. Goodpaster. Frame 14: Color guard.
- Contact Sheet 14769, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 42 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam foreign troops (Australia) - Aussie Pix sheet #4 - Brian Tidyman.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam foreign troops (Australia) - Brian Tidyman.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #4 in sequence: 3 more shots Kiwi infantry. 1 shot Land Rover crashing through jungle on way to retrieve VC car. 2 more shots of New Zealand infantry. 26 shots of recovery of VC Citroen. Note closeups of license plate NVA 601. Shots of Kiwi and Aussie troops hauling and pushing car through jungle. 1 shot of Aussie driver of land rover. Brian Tidyman driving through jungle. 3 shots of fire support base Flinders from the air -- note guns and jungle beyond perimeter.
- Contact Sheet 14770, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam (field day) - 1st Lt. Bob Blair - Sp5 Thomas Lauck - Sp4 Joel Perry - field day roll #2.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Field day - 1st Lt. Bob Blair - Sp5 Thomas Lauck - Sp4 Joel Perry.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 2 in sequence - 1 shot GI dropping ping-pong ball during ping-pong race. 1 shot GI trying to balance ping-pong ball on paddle during ping-pong race. 1 shot of GI trying to pick up ping-pong ball while another races to the finish line. 2 shots of GIs running quarter mile race. 1 shot of winner, Sp4 Joel Perry, crossing finish line. 1 shot of 3-legged race. 10 shots of tug-o-war. Anchor man for tug-o-war team looses his balance, falls, and is dragged. 2 shots of Sp5 Thomas Lauck eating pie -- he won contest. 1 shot 1st Lt Bob Blair stuffing his mouth with apple pie.
- Contact Sheet 14771, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - field day roll #1
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Field day.
- Contact Sheet 14772, 1968 December 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - field day roll #3 - Sp4 Nicholas Aguilar - Sp4 Joseph Gomez - 1st Lt. Bob Blair - Sp5 Thomas Lauck - pie eating contest.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Field day - pie eating contest - Sp4 Nicholas Aguilar - Sp4 Joseph Gomez - 1st Lt. Bob Blair - Sp4 Thomas Lauk.
- Contact Sheet 14773, 1968 December 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - animals - Pfc. Chester Clark - Pfc. Earnest Devine - Snake's tale - sheet E.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet E in sequence: 10 shots of Lind and playmate Ug-go. 3 shots of your intrepid OW photographer as I pet Ug-go, Ug-go tries to climb on me, and I point to the Bao-Chi label on my hat and try to convince the python that I'm really a noncombatant and that I wouldn't make a decent meal anyhow. 3 shots of Ug-go in the rafters of the personnel shop with Lind talking to him. 1 shot for story on sniper school Pfc Chester Clark spots targets for Pfc Earnest Devine (background, holding rifle).
- Contact Sheet 14774, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam animals python - Sgt. Richard Lind - snake's tale - sheet D.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for snake's tale story - Sheet D in sequence: Various shots of Sgt Richard Lind playing with Ug-go, the playful python as Ug-go crawls over Lind's anatomy (maybe measuring Lind up for a potential meal several years hence?).
- Contact Sheet 14775, 1968 October 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam army schools - Sniper school - Sfc. Albert Nainoa - SSGT Arpail Gapo - Sgt. Jimmy Hamblin - sheet F - story printed October / 7 / '68.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet for story on sniper school - Sheet F in sequence: - 3 shots of instructor Sfc Albert Nainoa sighting and firing at target using student's rifle. 2 shots S Sgt Arpail Gapo: looking through telescope at targets. 4 shots of Sfc Nainoa firing at the target (4th shot is blured because of recoil -- note expanded cartridge flying past Sfc Nainoa's right wrist). 7 shots of Sgt Jimmy Hamblin looking through ART (scope on top of rifle). 1 shot of student snipers and observers.
- Contact Sheet 14776, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam army schools - Sniper school - Pfc. Ken Britton - SSGT William Lee - sheet G.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam Army School (Snipers) - Pfc. Ken Britton - S. Sgt. William Lee - sheet G.
- Contact Sheet 14777, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam orphanage - roll 1 - Vietnam food - Sp5 Dean Jungers.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam orphanage - Sp5 Dean Jungers.
- Contact Sheet 14778, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam orphanage roll 2 - Sp5 Dean Jungers - Sp5 William Hunt.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sp5 William Hunt - Sp5 Dean Jungers.
- Contact Sheet 14779, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam patrol - Pfc. Don Patton - Pfc. Ron Oreskovich - Pfc. Louis Wilcox.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam patrol - Pfc. Don Patton - Pfc. Ron Oreskovich - Pfc. Louis Wilcox - Sp4 Ken Sona - sheet #1.
- Contact Sheet 14780, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam patrol - Sgt. Wardell Richardson - Pfc. Louis Wilcox - Sp4 Bob Drew - part demo scan / med.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Combat patrol of B Co. - Sgt. Wardell Richardson - Pfc. Louis Wilcox - Sp4 Bob Drew - #2.
- Contact Sheet 14781, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam patrol - Mike Roberts - Sp4 Bob Drew - Pfc. Richard Miller.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam patrol - Mike Roberts - Sp4 Bob Drew - Pfc. Richard Miller - approaching choppers.
- Contact Sheet 14782, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam rescue (by chopper).
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Choppers picking up GIs.
- Contact Sheet 14783, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam patrol - infantry - chopper rescue.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for combat patrol story - Roll #4 in sequence: 1 shot troops pop smoke to mark their position for choppers. 2 shots chopper ready to lift off. 1 shot chopper in flight.
- Contact Sheet 14795, 1968 December 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Dr. Gunnar Christiansen - eye treatment.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for story on dog's cornea transplant: 3 shots of Dr. Gunnar Christiansen examining a patient's eye. Also included is a 5 x 7 print of actual operation taken by GI medic, Sp5 Larry L. Ratliff.
- Contact Sheet 14804, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - General Kenneth Hodson - army US officers.
- Contact Sheet 14805, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - girls of Saigon - sheets 2 & 3.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: #2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheet for Girls of Saigon - Various candid shots of the belles of Saigon as they take a Sunday stroll.
- Contact Sheet 14806, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: #1.
- Contact Sheet 14807, 1968 December 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - hero: 1st Lt. Hulon Allen - story printed Dec./ 28 / '68- Jan / 4 / '69.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Shots 25-31 (For Hero story): Hero...1st Lt Hulon Allen.
- Contact Sheet 14809, 1968 December 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam entertainment - Tex Ritter - sheet A.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Entertainment - Tex Ritter - "the Bollweavils" (Wayne Gray, Billy Sprout, Kent Westberry) - Sheet A.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for Tex Ritter Story - In sequence: 2 shots color guard before start of show. 1 shot base commander with the Bollweavils in background. 1 shot the Bollweavils (Left to right Wayne Gray, electronic guitar, Billy Sprout, drums, Kent Westberry, electric guitar). 5 shots audience reation to Tex's songs. 3 shots Tex playing guitar, various angles. 2 shots of show from rear of hangar. 2 more shots of Tex playing guitar. 3 shots audience reaction to show. 1 shot Tex making small talk into mike. 3 more shots audience reaction. 3 shots Tex gesturing while singing. 7 shots of Tex and Bollweavils with audience in foreground.
- Contact Sheet 14810, 1968 December
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - entertainment - Tex Ritter sheet B.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Entertainment - Tex Ritter.
- Contact Sheet 14811, 1968 December 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam entertainment - Tex Ritter - sheet C.
- Contact Sheet 14812, 1968 December 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Bien Hoa (off limits) - women - Reynolds.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo ID -- Roll A: Reynolds - Shot 1: Deputy Sherif jeep. 2: An army lieutenant playing Boy Scout and helping an old lady across street. 3: for Bien Hoa off limits story: Long Binh has cafeterias. 4: Clubs. 5, 6: Same as 4. 7, 8: Traveling snack bars. 9, 10, 11, 12, 13: But what the guys really want is girls... These female type day laborers swing a pick and shovel all morning, but at noon, a Long Binh GI can whip 300 pee on many of them for a short time in his room or in a Conex. 14: for Biem Hoa story: A row of Conex's - a handy place for a noon-hour sex break with the day labor force. 15: Seedy villages surround Long Binh post, but are off limits to all military.
- Contact Sheet 14813, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam currency conversion.
- Contact Sheet 14814, 1968 December 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - food (rice story) - Cpl. Robert Anderson - Cpl. T. K. Marple - Sgt. Dennnis Guy.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Rice story.
- Contact Sheet 14815, 1969 January 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - hospitals - miscellaneous - Seaman Ken Guyer - E-4 Dwight Gievers - E4 skipper - story in Jan / 11 / '69 edition.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo IDs - miscellaneous - Reynolds - Frames 2-5: The hospital Ship Helgoland at Danang. 6-9: Seaman Ken Guyer tools the 45-foot harbor patrol boat around Danang harbor. 10: Captain E-4 Dwight Gievers aboard his ship - Gievers is left. 11-12: The patrol boat pulls away from dock to go back on routine patrol.
- Contact Sheet 14816, 1968 December 21
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Capt. John Kapranopoulos - crimes - acquittal - lst Lt. Ralph Loomis -1st Lt. Joe Harris.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Dec. 2 - ID for Contact Sheet X -- for K murder trial - Frame 5: Loomis (left) and Harris, star prosecution witnesses, outside courtroom. Frame 6: Kapranopoulos ducks camera after his defense lawyer, Kulish had just scuffled with the OW photog to prevent a picture. Frame 7: Kulish smirks at photographer. Frame 8: Kulish (left) and Kapranopoulos (arrow) speed across road.
- Contact Sheet 14817, 1968 December 14
  Contact sheet containing 2 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - entertainment - Tippie Hedren - Joe Bishop - Sfc. J. Neese - Dec./ 14 / '68 / Pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Nov. 25 - Joey Bishop story: Men of 71st Trans Bn at Newport, pose outside mess hall with Joey Bishop (civilian clothes) and actress Tippie Hedren. Man on right is battalion mess sergeant, Sfc J. Neese.
- Contact Sheet 14818, 1968 July 20
  Contact sheet containing 1 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Ronnie T. Milner - Capt. Kurt P. Schulke - crimes - shooting.
- Contact Sheet 14819, 1968 December 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - Sp4 Thomas S. Gray - Capt. George Henning (defense).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Nov. 25 - ID for contact sheet AA -- All for Gray murder trial - Frames 3-4: Gray. Frame 5: Don Hirst. Frame 6-7: Gray (right) with guard, in witness room during trial break. Frames 8-10: Gray, handcuffed after hearing verdict with MP guard - guard locks handcuffs on Gray while assistant defense counsel, Capt. George Henning, watches.
- Contact Sheet 14820, 1968 December
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sneaky Forces - supplies - camps - monuments - not printed - A.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Monument to KIAs from "A" company located at company Hq, Bien Hoa. 2a: The company supply dump ready-line. Supplies for "A" comps… and ready to be delivered by convoy to intermediate "B" Det supply points for further delivery to "A" camps, either by air-drop, LOLEX (low-level parachute extraction from cargo plane) or by regular aircraft ferry if airstrip is usable and camp is secure enough for aircraft to land. 4a: Truck loaded with supplies and ready to roll in convoy to a "B" det camp. 5a: Another truck. 6a: Parachute Rigger folding cargo chute in rigging shed. Chutes are used for air drop of supplies to "A" camps where aircraft can't land. 7a: Rigger. 8a: Rigger. 9a: Vietnamese pallet builders mass produce wooden pallets for shipment of cargo. Two carpenters sawing a pile of timbers to be used in building pallets. 10a: Same-same 9a. 11a: same same. 12: Gas point at company Hq. 13a: Sign on gas point. 14a: CIDG program vehicles get regular check-up each morning before going to work (Vehicles don't belong to US. Belong to CIDG program, so they don't carry the US white Star or US Army markings.) 15a: COs jeep gets inspection each morning too. 16a: Crap. Disregard. 17a: Entrance to company Hq camp. 18a: samesame. 19a: Monument to dead guys (again, only with flags this time). 20a: More crap. Disregard. 21: ?????? Extra foto shot to be shooting extra film.
- Contact Sheet 14821, 1968 December
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - camps - Sneaky Forces - 2B.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo ID -- Sneaky Forces - 1: 500 pound bomb craters from B52 strikes in support of SF camp which was under heavy attack late in September. 2: Air shots of typical "Star" A-team camp. 3: Same. 4: Same. 5: Same. White spots at top are bomb-craters from air strikes. 6: Same. Points of star are manned by CIDG people -- Vietnamese, Montanard, Cambodian, Chinese Nung etc. More-or-less-circle is road around pentagon-shaped US camp in center. US camp is surrounded by barb-wire, concertina and claymores. Star is surrounded by barb-wire, concertina, trip wires, punji pits, claymores, earth berms, mines, guys with guns and other assorted nasty things. Charlie camps in woods just beyond cleared fire-fields. 7: Another same. 8: ????? Double exposure. 9: Engineers at camp repairing damage done by Charlie's September attack and building bunker-homes for CIDG forces and their families (families of CIDG types live in most camps with the CIDGs). Bunker-homes are on perimeter of star. 10: Same.
- Contact Sheet 14822, 1968 December 6
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - camps - Sneaky Forces - 3C.